<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Quizy</string>
    <string name="says">Challenge your mind \n unlock your potential. \n Welcome to Quizy!</string>
    <string name="info">Using our Quiz App, you get an exhilarating journey of knowledge and entertainment at your fingertips. Ignite your curiosity, challenge your limits, and boost your brainpower with brain-teasing quizzes. Enjoy instant learning gratification, connect with others through friendly competition, and stay updated on the latest trends. With our flexible and gamified approach to education, you\'ll boost confidence, track your progress, and experience continuous improvement. Dive into a world where learning meets excitement, only with Quiz App</string>
    <string name="info2">Ignite Curiosity: Unleash the power of curiosity! Quiz applications spark a thirst for knowledge, inviting users to explore and discover fascinating facts in an interactive and engaging way. Brain Boosting Entertainment: Elevate your entertainment experience! Engage your mind with challenging quizzes that not only entertain but also stimulate cognitive functions, keeping your brain in top-notch condition. Challenge Your Limits: Break through your limits! Quiz applications provide a platform to challenge and surpass your own knowledge boundaries, turning every quiz session into a thrilling adventure of self-discovery. Instant Learning Gratification: Instant knowledge, instant gratification! Receive immediate feedback on your quiz performance, turning learning into a rewarding and satisfying experience right at your fingertips. Social Connection: Quiz applications bring people together! Compete with friends, family, or even globally, fostering a sense of friendly competition and shared enthusiasm for learning. Stay Updated and Informed: Stay ahead of the curve! Quiz applications keep you updated on the latest trends, events, and facts, ensuring you are always in the know and ready to impress with your knowledge. Flexibility in Learning: Learn on your terms! Quiz applications offer a flexible learning environment, allowing users to absorb information at their own pace and on their own schedule. Gamified Education: Education meets excitement! Transform the learning process into an enjoyable game, making education not only effective but also a thrilling experience that users look forward to. Boost Confidence: Supercharge your confidence! Successfully answering quiz questions boosts self-esteem and confidence, empowering users to feel more knowledgeable and accomplished.</string>
    <string name="back">Do you want to finish your test? If you do, your results will not be saved</string>
</resources>